Mildred Gilman Wohlforth Papers, 1910-1994 (bulk 1927-1985 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 4: Printed Matter, 1981-1989; more than 6 folders
  - Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated; 4 folders (Box 22, Folder 4-7)
  - Clippings: Laminated, undated; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Magazines, undated; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Series 5: Papers of Robert Wohlforth, 1934; 2 boxes
  - Subseries 5A: Correspondence, undated; 4 folders
    - A-F, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Farrar, Straus Giroux, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - G-L, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - M-Z, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 5B: Articles, undated; 15 folders
    - Doran story, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - The Durable Malloy, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Father Nature, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Future Generals, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - The Grand Jury of the Nation, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - I Am a Freudian, Profile of Smith Ely Jeliffe, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - I Married a Sob Sister, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - The Mechanical Brain, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Mildred the Mulcher, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - A Nickelodeon Childhood, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Radio Play, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Reel Up the Hose, Martin, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - A Rising, Young Broadway Producer, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Synopsis of a Clerical Error, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - What's Blocking our Scientific Research, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 5C: Documents and Miscellaneous Papers, undated; 1 folder
    - Documents and Miscellaneous Papers, undated; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 5D: Printed Matter, 1934; 4 folders
    - Reviews of Tin Soldiers, 1934; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - The Princeton Library in New York, undated; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Tearsheets of articles, undated; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Clippings: miscellaneous, undated; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Series 6: Photographs, undated; more than 13 folders
  - People: General, A-Z, undated; 1 folder
    - Addams, Charles, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Durbin, Deanna, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Göring, Hermann, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Hansl, Helen, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Hitler, Adolf, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Huntley, Mildred Bob, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Kelly, Tommy, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Le Galliénne, Eva, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Longworth, Alice, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Myrdal, Alva Gunar, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Power, Tyrone, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Riefenstahl, Leni, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Stengel, Hans, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Withers, Jane, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Woodring, Carl, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Broun, Heywood, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Parker, Dorothy, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Robeson, Paul, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Shaw, George Bernard McFadden, Bernard, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Temple, Shirley, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Wohlforth, Mildred Gilman, undated; 2 folders (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
  - Wohlforth, Robert, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Children, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified People, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Dive in the Hackensack River, N.J., undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Henry Colin Campbell, “Torch Killer”, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Places Things, undated; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 14)